# **MOHAMED SALAH**

### FLUTTER DEVEOLPER

mohamed\_salah\_414@yahoo.com

#### **SUMMARY**

Always up for a challenge, I have worked for freelancers' sites and gotten more experience from companies and start-ups where I worked with. I have a **Bs.** in **Computer Science** and many years of experience in designing and marketing before going into **flutter** development. that helped me to improve in **UI/UX** design at the same time developing **flutter** apps.

#### **CONTACT DETAILS**

Mobile: (+20)1203650266

E-mail: mohamed\_salah\_414@yahoo.com Website: https://mohamedsalah414.github.io/

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohamedsalah414/ GitHub: https://github.com/mohamedsalah414 Dribbble: https://dribbble.com/mohamedsalah414

#### **SKILLS**

- Dart OOP
- Data Structure Algorithms
- MVVM pattern Clean Architecture
- Riverpod Provider GetX Bloc
- Dio Http retrofit
- RESTful API error handling
- Firebase Firestore and Auth
- Push Notification local Notification
- Sqflite Hive
- Shared preferences
- Authentication system
- PayPal Payment Integration (WebView)
- Google Maps
- Pusher Channel Chat
- Git (GitHub) CI/CD (GitHub actions)
- Sound & Video integration
- Work with Adobe XD & Figma

#### **EDUCATION**

Alexandria University
 Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science
 Sep 2016 - Jul 2021

#### **LANGUAGUE**

- Arabic (Native)
- English (Very Good)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Flojics
 Flutter developer · Full-time

From Office
Jun 2023 – Present
Alexandria, Egypt

Rare Crew

Flutter developer · Full-time

Remotely Nov 2022 – Feb 2023 Alexandria, Egypt

Coappso

Flutter developer · Full-time

From Office Mar 2022 – Nov 2022 Alexandria, Egypt

Freelancing

Flutter developer · Freelancer

Feb 2021 – Mar 2022 Alexandria, Egypt

#### **PROJECTS**

# **Casting (Actor side)**

Each actor can browse and apply for each director's projects from films, advertisements, or filming sessions, and can view his own photos and videos, and create his own photo gallery, explaining his technical and personal specifications.

# Hera (Customer side)

Ladies can book appointments to go to the beauty center and browse the services and products and chat with the beauty center.

## **Gym System (User & Trainer sides)**

The user can book a training session in the gym with or without his personal trainer using the application's coins and can search across the map for the nearest branches, specify directions to them, browse the trainers' photos and videos, and message them and the gym as well.

# Clinic System (Patient side)

The patient can browse the clinics and doctors and book the appropriate appointment for him, and he can chat with the clinic.

# Hiring System (Company side)

Each company can create its own account that contains all its information and can search for employees to hire them based on some of the requirements specified by the company.

# **Reminder Religious App**

The application contains the Holy Qur'an without the Internet or ads and contains translation, interpretation, and reading in the voice of the sheikhs, and the user can activate the notifications for the call to prayer and remind him of some religious supplications.

# **E\_Approvals - IMG Licensing**



E\_Approvals is a platform for managing and tracking the approval process for product images, logos, and branding. It is used in the licensing industry to streamline the review and approval of images used in product packaging, advertising, and other materials.

### Mo Salah Portfolio



A portfolio app shows my work, skills & achievements in my whole career as a Flutter developer with more than one year experience.

### **3ilagy Time**



Stay on top of your health with our app's easy-to-use reminders for medications and other important health-related tasks.

#### Mo'zen



With our app, you can easily set reminders and receive notifications for every prayer time, ensuring that you never miss a prayer, also features a Qibla compass that allows you to find the direction of the Kaaba in Mecca.